Hey, old friend? How do we stay old friends?
Merrily We Roll Along is a comedy, music film directed by Maria Friedman.
Franklin Shepard is a talented Broadway composer who abandons his theater career and
all his friends in New York in order to produce films in Los Angeles.
The story begins at the height of his Hollywood fame and moves backwards in time, showing
snapshots of the most important moments in Frank’s life that shaped the man he is today.
A live recording of the 2024 Tony Award-winning Broadway revival of Stephen Sondheim and
George Furth's musical, filmed at the Hudson Theatre in New York City.
Franklin Shepard, played by Jonathan Groff.
Mary Flynn, played by Lindsay Mendez.
Charley Kringas, played by Daniel Radcliffe.
Gussie Carnegie, played by Krystal Joy Brown.
Beth Shepard, played by Katie Rose Clarke.
Joe Josephson, played by Reg Rogers.
Merrily We Roll Along is an upcoming American epic musical film written and directed by Richard Linklater, based on the
1981 musical by Stephen Sondheim and George Furth, which is in turn adapted from the 1934 play by George S.
Kaufman and Moss Hart.
Jason Blum serves as a producer under his Blumhouse Productions banner.
Starring Paul Mescal, Ben Platt, and Beanie Feldstein, the production began principal photography in 2019, although an unknown amount
was reshot in 2021 following the casting of Paul Mescal, and it is unclear how much of the film from 2019 will be used.
The film explores themes of friendship, musical, based on
play or musical, coming of age, broadway.
The tone is lighthearted.